const tasksSelect = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'The metal object that hangs on the wall and keeps us warm.',
    variant1: 'air-condition',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'carpet',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'radiator',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      'The object that hangs on the wall and blows out hot or cold air.',
    variant1: 'ceiling',
    variant2: 'socket',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'air-condition',
    correct: 'air-condition',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'This is made from glass and you can look outside through this.',
    variant1: 'switch',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'window',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'The top part of the room where the lights usually are.',
    variant1: 'air-condition',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'ceiling',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      'This is usually made from wood and you can enter or leave a room through it.',
    variant1: 'floor',
    variant2: 'door',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'door',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'The bottom part of the room where the carpet usually is.',
    variant1: 'air-condition',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'floor',
    variant4: 'light',
    correct: 'floor',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      'There are usually four of these in the room above the floor but below the ceiling.',
    variant1: 'door',
    variant2: 'heating',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'wall',
    correct: 'wall',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'This is a colourful and sometimes beautiful decoration we put on the floor.',
    variant1: 'carpet',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'carpet',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'The plastic object where you can plug your electronic items such as a computer or TV.',
    variant1: 'carpet',
    variant2: 'radiator',
    variant3: 'socket',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'socket',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      'The plastic object you have to press to turn the lights on and off.',
    variant1: 'switch',
    variant2: 'socket',
    variant3: 'window',
    variant4: 'ceiling',
    correct: 'switch',
  },
];

export default tasksSelect;
